Guide to the Stanford Museum Collection
Stanford University Library
- Museum objects
  - Fencing vest used by student in 1895/6, ARCH-AM-2000-032 (Box 1)
    see also ACCN 2000-297 for photo of student and fencing master
  - Figure of football and football shoe with plaque "GERHARD CASPER 2000 Rose Bowl Kickoff Luncheon", ARCH-AM-2000-019 (Box 1)
  - Figure of gold miner on base with plaque "In Honor of PRESIDENT G. CASPER GUEST SPEAKER Stanford Sacramento Club 30 March 1993", ARCH-AM-2000-018 (Box 1)
  - Fire place bellows with many initials names, inc. Bruce Bliven, classes '14, '16, '17. 56x24x5 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-266 (Box 1)
  - First academic robe of President Hennessy, ARCH-AM-2003-002 (Box 1)
  - Five (5) "Beat Cal" buttons, 1978-1981, ARCH-AM-1993-04 (Box 1)
  - Flag: French tri-color; possibly used by Stanford ambulance corps during World War I, ARCH-AM-2000-064 (Box 1)
  - Football autographed by Glenn Warner Team, ARCH-AM-1978-03 (Box 1)
  - Football banner, ca. 1895. Red cowhide; canvas glued on leather with painting of Stanford coed and football player. Irregular shape, approx. 3 x 3 ft., ARCH-AM-1977-09 (Box 1)
  - Football bracelet: chains in shape of footballs, dated 1932, 1935, 1937, 1938, 1940 (3), 1941 all re Frankie Albert, ARCH-AM-1991-021 (Box 1)
  - Football charms, each engraved directly, ARCH-AM-1978-13 (Box 1)
    1: 1908 / J.R. Pemberton forward / Intercollegiate Champions 2: 1908 / Pacific Coast Champions / Stanford 6 California 3: 1907 Intercollegiate Champions / J.R. Pemberton forward
  - Football pin: Stanford "S" lapel pin, with small football suspended below., ARCH-AM-1980-21 (Box 1)
  - Football Referee's yellow flag (for calling penalties). NOT one used in any Big Game., ARCH-AM-2000-028 (Box 1)
  - football socks ca. 1897; red wool. An addition to AM 79-12, ARCH-AM-1981-05 (Box 1)
  - Football sweater, athletic, heavy red wool, knit, long sleeve, turtle neck. 73 x 47 cm., ARCH-AM-1984-42 (Box 1)
  - Football uniform ca. 1896, worn by Darwin B. Lyon Jr., ARCH-AM-1978-07 (Box 1)
  - Football, Big Game, ca. 1892 [alleged], ARCH-AM-1984-45 (Box 1)
  - Football, reputed to be from first big game, ARCH-AM-1978-06 (Box 1)
  - Football: no laces, ARCH-AM-1994-07 (Box 1)
  - Form Board. Psychological Apparatus, 1930. 34x46 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-107.2 (Box 1)
  - Founders' Day button: "Celebrate Stanford! Founders' Day April 9, 2000" with image of all 3 Stanfords in center, ARCH-AM-2000-003 (Box 1)
  - Frame from portrait of Homer Laughlin, class of 1896:; Leather, tooled design, padded. [for photo see GP 15693], ARCH-AM-1995-19 (Box 1)
  - Framed collage of women's basketball team 1896, ARCH-AM-1982-13 (Box 1)
  - Framed Letter Envelope: 22x28 glass. To Mother's Club of Stanford; from Subversive Activities Commitee, 1956., ARCH-AM-2000-250 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo (1903) of the chancel in Memorial Church, showing 5 of the statues of the saints, ARCH-AM-2001-08 (Box 1)
  - Framed Photo of Jane Stanford Leland, Jr. Sepia in gold frame 988x61 cm). Jane faces left., ARCH-AM-2000-261 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo of the Stanford Faculty Winter quarter, 1914. panoramic view taken in inner quad. this is a duplicate, ARCH-AM-2000-010 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo of view of campus over Lake Lagunita, pre-1906, ARCH-AM-2001-09 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo reproduction of bird's eye view of Ayrshire Farm, residence of Peter Coutts [same as print 179] Frame OD 38x46cm, image 14x21cm., ARCH-AM-2000-361 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo, Breakers Club Stanford Fall 1910. BW Photo. Has some info pasted over glass regarding members. [duplicate of GP2806], ARCH-AM-2000-360 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo, BW, Stanford Stock Farm, view of barns. frame OD 28x36cm, image 27x34cm. - DUPLICATE OF GP OS 12726., ARCH-AM-2000-362 (Box 1)
  - Framed photo, Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 5 color photos of SLAC-- exterior and interior. Description on reverse. frame 39x33cm. photos= 5(8x11cm color photos)., ARCH-AM-2000-363 (Box 1)
  - framed photograph of El Palo Alto, ca. 1900., ARCH-AM-2002-19 (Box 1)
    Typed inscription reads:My Dad and Mother came to Stanford in 1897, just after their marriage, my father having been hired by David Starr Jordan, President of Stanford. This photo of the beautiful old Palo Alto Tree, circa 1900, was always proudly displayed in our home. This tree rested by the railroad bridge on the north end of Palo Alto.
  - Framed photograph of view of campus over Lake Lagunita, ca. 1905. Gymnasium completed, library not completed., ARCH-AM-2001-17 (Box 1)
  - Framed photograph of William F. Durand, ARCH-AM-1993-06 (Box 1)
  - Framed photos of Nora Stanford Wells and her husband Mr. Wells. Frames were once hinged together, but hinges are now broken, ARCH-AM-2006-008 (Box 1)
  - Framed photos, color and BW, ARCH-AM-2000-365 (Box 1)
    1. William J. Bonsall, 1934, BW. frame 41x21cm, image 5x9 2. Mr. and Mrs. Samuel Bonsall, color. frame 41x21cm, image 11x8cm. 3. Text re Memorial fund for 3 professorships and library.
  - Framed Piece of Paper. Glass. "Dr. J.C. Branner to H.C. Hoover, Nove. 30 1893- for services during Month of November, $9.80 et." 13 x 26 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-265 (Box 1)
  - Framed Portrait: Judge Samuel F. Lieb, oil painting, in gold frame., ARCH-AM-2000-259 (Box 1)
  - Framed prints (large, ornate frames) of Brian Lamprell's color sketches of Stanford views 1998, ARCH-AM-2005-022 (Box 1)
    2005-022.1 Memorial Church 2005-022.2 Main Quad [really inner quad] 2005-022.3 Palm Drive 2005-022.4 Green Library [West Wing front view]
  - Framed reproduction of artist's rendering of Memorial Church (possibly post-quake reconstruction) front oblique view, exterior. frame OD 36x48cm, image 21x38cm., ARCH-AM-2000-364 (Box 1)
  - Framed sepia photos of arboretum view, ARCH-AM-1995-24 (Box 1)
  - Framed under glass, 33X25 cm. Stanford Daily headlines, 1938-40 collage style., ARCH-AM-2000-178 (Box 1)
  - Framed- Stanford Coeds c. 1895. Series of Individual Portraits., ARCH-AM-2000-357 (Box 1)
  - Framed; Resolution of Sympathy re death of Jane Stanford, signed by members of Stanford Club of S.F. frame 55x50, image 45x39 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-306 (Box 1)
  - Free standing photo frame, possibly brass, ornate trim., ARCH-AM-1992-08 (Box 1)
  - French "Croix de Guerre" from flag pole (US flag used by Stanford Ambulance Corps??), ARCH-AM-2000-065.1 (Box 1)
  - French horn #12393 in case "Property of Stanford University Bands", ARCH-AM-1999-018 (Box 1)
  - freshman "dink" (cap) from 1917, ARCH-AM-1993-08 (Box 1)
  - Frisbee: "Sequoia Travel Center, Tresidder Union" red white, ARCH-AM-1985-08 (Box 1)
  - glass jar with label: "Varian 50th Anniversary Blackberry Jam", ARCH-AM-1999-003 (Box 1)
  - Gold key presented to Mrs. Lucie Stern by SU in appreciation for her gift of Ruth Lucie Stern Research Lab, 1939, St. Med., ARCH-AM-1977-02 (Box 1)
  - Gold pocket watch (1919) and wedding ring of Chester Naramore, with suede leather pouch, 1919 and undated; ARCH-AM-2009-026 (Box 1)
    2009-026.1 Watch is engraved inside: "Chet" in appreciation from Petroleum Division U.S.B.M. Feb. 1st 1919; outside has initials entwined CN 2009-026.2 Ring is engraved: G.E.C. to C. N. 2009-026.3 Suede pouch
  - Graduation tassel Class of 2002, ARCH-AM-2010-005 (Box 1)
  - Greek marble piece from fireplace mantel, incised with "S", ARCH-AM-2005-031 (Box 1)
  - Green armband issued to faculty observers to be used during campus disturbances, 1971; ARCH-AM-2010-015 (Box 1)
  - Green Teas Stanford Libraries 2008-2009, coffee cup (white with black interior), ARCH-AM-2009-021 (Box 1)
  - Gym Suit: black bloomers, white shirt, black sash, black vest, c. 1900., ARCH-AM-1983-05 (Box 1)
  - Hard hat - white with Stanford seal on front; used during Library basement remodeling, ARCH-AM-1979-16 (Box 1)
  - Hard hat - white with Stanford seal on front; used during Library basement remodeling, ARCH-AM-1979-17 (Box 1)
  - Hard hat (1) White, on front: "The Leland Stanford Mansion;" on back: "Team Stanford Mansion." Baseball Cap (1) Red, on front: "Stanford Football" (with "S" Logo)., undated; ARCH-AM-2009-033 (Box 1)
    2009-033.1 White hard hat 2009-033.2 Red baseball cap
  - Hat (beanie style) and red tie with L'Il Injun design painted on it, ca. 1951, ARCH-AM-2006-001 (Box 1)
    2006-001.1 Hat 2006-001.2 Tie
  - Hat, 1912, writing on brim, red, "Stanford, Stanford, Hurrah, Hurro" '12., ARCH-AM-1984-25 (Box 1)
  - Hat, beanie, 9x21, gray with red button, size 6 7/8, ARCH-AM-1984-28 (Box 1)
  - Hat, Plug Ugly. 1905. of R.S. Lewis, ARCH-AM-2000-106 (Box 1)
  - Hat, red and white, '12, 28x21x13cm., ARCH-AM-1984-27 (Box 1)
  - Hat, red felt with thin white band. 28 x 25cm., ARCH-AM-1984-46 (Box 1)
  - Hat, Senior Sombrero, Maker = The Regent, Palo Alto. 32x99x11 cm., ARCH-AM-1984-26 (Box 1)
  - Hat: Sombero: c. 1908, signatures of '08, '09, '03. "R. L. Holman on brim., ARCH-AM-2000-268 (Box 1)
  - Hats - sombrero and plug ugly, ARCH-AM-1997-012 (Box 1)
    1. Senior Sombrero - leather band with "Stanford 11"; S.B.S. on inner band 2. Plug Ugly, S.B.S. class of 1911 - paintings: Encina Club, History, woman's face, 1911 banner
  - Hats and beanies, ARCH-AM-1983-07 (Box 1)
    0. freshman beanie, gray 1. felt hat, red, with gray band 2. felt hat, red; 3. leather belt, brown, with buckle, "Stanford" 4. leather hat band for a senior "Sombrero" 5. ribbon, red and blue, with small buckle
  - Hats: 1 sophomore dink, 1 baseball hat (red felt), ARCH-AM-1981-07 (Box 1)
  - Herbert Hoover Medal for Distinguished Service presented to J. Wallace Sterling by Stanford Alumni Association with case, 1964; ARCH-AM-2009-012 (Box 1)
  - Herbert Hoover Medal for Distinguished Service, Stanford Alumni Association ["blank" - not awarded to anyone], undated (pre-1985); ARCH-AM-2009-013 (Box 1)
  - High heeled shoes originally with Carol Green's scrapbook, ARCH-AM-1996-01 (Box 1)
  - High School Musical 3 doll: Off to College Gabriella (in Stanford outfit), 2008; ARCH-AM-2009-042 (Box 1)
    Copy 1 is missing the "Disney" sticker on upper left of original box. Copy 2 [added March 2010] is complete.
  - homemade tag, small banner for 75th anniversay (2000), an award plaque from Children's Wish Foundation International (includes photo of APO member with a child at a playground), Golden Anniversary seal, hand puppet in shape of a beaver, and Playskool Cobbler's Bench labeled "APO Female Presidents' Gavel", ARCH-AM-2007-013 (Box 1)
    2007-013.1 tag 2007-013.2 small banner 2007-013.3 plaque 2007-013.4 Golden anniversary seal 2007-013.5 beaver puppet 2007-013.6 "Female Presidents' Gavel."
  - Honor the Game - button and brochure re program sponsored by Positive Coaching Alliance, ARCH-AM-2002-17 (Box 1)
  - Hoover House construction materials, 2001: Original roofing tile and sample of new replacement tile, ARCH-AM-2002-04 (Box 1)
  - Horn, used at Big Game March 1892. 22 inches, tin; barely readable on shaft of horn is "Ball Game L.S.J. U. [v?] UC March 19, 1892" and the name Harriett J. Fyffe. On the fluted edge is "Rah, Rah, Rah / Rah, Rah" and the name Minnie B. Yoder, ARCH-AM-2000-033 (Box 1)
  - Horn, used at Stanford-Nebraska Rose Bowl game, 1941; by Roos Bros.; red/white, ARCH-AM-2000-034 (Box 1)
  - Horseshoe, ARCH-AM-1992-10 (Box 1)
  - Indian doll with bendable arms and legs, originally owned by Walt Peterson, ARCH-AM-1997-011 (Box 1)
  - Insulated coffee cup with lid "Stanford Bookstore Cafe Confections" ca. 1995, ARCH-AM-2007-030 (Box 1)
  - Invitation to party for Sandy Riser - inside a paper cup with plastic stick, ARCH-AM-1993-14 (Box 1)
  - Ivory handled razor, "Francis B. Loomis" on handle., ARCH-AM-2000-151.1 (Box 1)
  - Ivory handled razor., ARCH-AM-2000-151.2 (Box 1)
  - J. L. Stanford portrait mask, ARCH-AM-2000-068.5 (Box 1)
  - Jacket, reversible red/khaki, with round patch "STANFORD BAND" around Indian head, ARCH-AM-2002-22 (Box 1)
  - Japanese Caligraphy in black frame with glass-110x65 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-088 (Box 1)
  - Jewelry- pins, money clip, ARCH-AM-1983-03 (Box 1)
    1. Pin: gold, red enamel, with seal of LSJU (1/2'"" diam.) origin: Donor Estates 2. Phi Beta Kappa Pin: gold on back: ""Zoe Watkins, Stanford, 1910,"" origin: Zoe L. Watkins, 1910 3. FOB: gold, red enamel, with seal of LSJU. Ring attached. On back: "Zoe L. Watkins, Kingman, Arizona" 14k. origin: Zoe L. Watkins 4. Pin: gold, black enamel pin in shape of mortarboard on back: "Zoe Watkins, 1910" 14k. origin: Zoe L. Watkins 5. Money Clip: silver, engraved: "Florence Loomis, Burlingame, California."
  - Jewelry: three small pins, incl. on lsju seal (.5cm diam) and two gold pins, ARCH-AM-1982-12 (Box 1)
  - Key chain; enameled picture (multi-colored) of front of quad from palm drive., ARCH-AM-1980-09 (Box 1)
  - Key, 4 cm long, "Key to trunk at Union Safe Deposit with C.P. Huntington. J.L.S. " labelled, ARCH-AM-2000-210 (Box 1)
  - Keychain, facsimile of Big Game 1981 ticket. Bronze colored metal. with ring., ARCH-AM-1982-08 (Box 1)
  - Klystron tubes (13), varying sizes; see accn. listing for complete details, ARCH-AM-1996-03 (Box 1)
  - Knobby Adaline - weather prediction machine buildt by Bernard Widrow; used in San Francisco, ca. 1960, ARCH-AM-1997-020 (Box 1)
  - Konrad B. Krauskopt medals with cases, 1960 and undated; ARCH-AM-2009-011 (Box 1)
    2009-011.1 Gold medal awarded by The Geological Society of American, 1960 2009-011.2 Gold medal awarded by The Geochemical Society, undated
  - L'il Injun decal, circa 1950; ARCH-AM-2009-003 (Box 1)
  - L'il Injun watch, ARCH-AM-1982-02 (Box 1)
  - L'il Injun window sticker, ARCH-AM-1982-03 (Box 1)
  - Label button "Happy Birthday Donald Tresidder" Apr. 6, 1979, ARCH-AM-1979-11 (Box 1)
  - label pin: "Stanford Basketball 1998-99 Season Celebrating 25 Years", ARCH-AM-1999-008 (Box 1)
  - Label: 5.5x7 cm, Color, Palo Alto Brand of Tomatoes., ARCH-AM-2000-202 (Box 1)
  - Lace bedspread (or possibly tablecloth) used by Hopkins [Lydia] 1873 and on, with two smaller cloths of same design., ARCH-AM-1989-188 (Box 1)
  - Ladies Pins., ARCH-AM-2000-211 (Box 1)
    2000-211.1 Ladies Stick Pin, with Lacey gold design. 2.5x3x5 cm. 2000-211.2 Ladies Stick Pin, with Lacey gold design. 2.5x3x5 cm.
  - Lantern Slide Projector (old) for 3" to 4" slides, ARCH-AM-2000-254 (Box 1)
  - Large bolt (2 of them) distributed as keepsakes at ground breaking ceremony for Cantor Center; third one came with accn 2008-107, ARCH-AM-1995-27 (Box 1)
  - large poster: duplication of framed axe, ARCH-AM-2002-14 (Box 1)
  - Large red felt rectangle with "STANFORD' in white letters; white satin along left edge with red/white streamers at three points., ARCH-AM-2001-05 (Box 1)
  - Large scale replica of "Think Again" cube (8 inch), undated; ARCH-AM-2009-036 (Box 1)
  - Laundry bag from Stanford Laundry of Palo Alto "Where Device Care Prolong Wear", ARCH-AM-2001-36 (Box 1)
  - Leaded glass window from Hoover House front door (plain glass)., ARCH-AM-2002-10 (Box 1)
  - Leather hat band: "Stanford 24", ARCH-AM-1999-014 (Box 1)
  - Leather piece from Stanford Harness - black leather with brass "S" on both sides, ARCH-AM-1995-31 (Box 1)
  - Leather postcards (2): ""Rah Rah Rah, Stanford"", ARCH-AM-2000-061 (Box 1)
    2000-061.1 red leather with white S; postmarked 1903 2000-061.2 brown leather with images of girl holding pennant; postmarked 1903
  - Leather postcards(12 of street scenes and athletics- 1907), sent to Myrtle Mabbott, ARCH-AM-1982-14 (Box 1)
  - Leland Stanford, Jr. 24X16cm image, 43X36cm frame. Purple velvet with gold corners. Tinted image on cerameic. Signed by Fr. Jill Dresden., ARCH-AM-2000-124 (Box 1)
  - Leland Stanford's pen and leather booklet for wiping it (entitled "Extracts from the pen of Senator Stanford"), ARCH-AM-2005-003 (Box 1)
    2005-003.1 pen 2005-003.2 leather booklet
  - Letter box that held correspondence of ASSU president Bruce Jessup, ARCH-AM-1995-17 (Box 1)
  - Letter form Board of Trustees to Jane L. Stanford, June 5th, 1903 (when trustees assume active care; states principals; no frame; 39x53 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-082 (Box 1)
  - Letter opener (5.25 in. long, silver) with University seal on handle. Still on original gift card; signed on reverse "From Garrett Elmore June 20, 1927", ARCH-AM-2009-002 (Box 1)
  - Letter sweater, Driggs recorded as swimmer (went to Olympics in '28). red knit with white S., ARCH-AM-1980-16 (Box 1)
  - Letterman's sweater of Tyler F. Woodward, class of 1924 - gold sweater with red S and 3 red stars, ARCH-AM-2005-035 (Box 1)
  - Library Perforator, circa 1892, 28x13x15 cm. heavy black metal, "Library Leland Stanford University", ARCH-AM-2000-101 (Box 1)
  - License plate holder "All Right Now!" "Stanford '80" - memento from 25th reunion of the Class of 1980 held in Fall of 2005., ARCH-AM-2005-037 (Box 1)
  - Lithograph- Horse "Palo Alto", ARCH-AM-2000-358 (Box 1)
  - Lockets, ARCH-AM-2000-216 (Box 1)
    2000-216.1 Locket, gold, 1.5x1cm, 1939 Senior Ball. 2000-216.2 Locket, gold, 1.5x1cm, 1939 Senior Ball. 2000-216.3 Locket, gold, 1.5x1cm, 1939 Senior Ball. 2000-216.4 Locket, gold, 1.5x1cm, 1939 Senior Ball.
  - Logo in metal: "VA varian", ARCH-AM-1999-009 (Box 1)
  - Loose issues of early Daily Palo Alto for possible exhibit use, 1898-1916., ARCH-AM-2003-003 (Box 1)
    Vol. 8-9: Sept. 2, 1898, Sept. 22, 1898, Mar. 1, 1899, Mar. 21, 1899, Mar. 24, 1899 Vol. 16: Jan. 12 - May 30, 1900 [including commencement issue] Vol. 17: Sept. - Dec. 1900 Vol. 27-36: 1905: Sept. 22, Oct. 5, Oct. 16, Oct. 18-20, Oct. 25 1907: Sept. 10-11 1908: Nov. 6, Nov. 10 1909: Jan. 5-6, Mar. 25 1910: Jan. 18-20, Apr. 28 Vol. 30 Jan. 8 - May 10, 1907. Missing issues: #8 Jan. 17, #36-37 Feb. 27-28; #66 Apr. 13 Vol. 35 Aug. 1909 - Dec. 9, 1909 [bound without boards]. Missing issues: #2-3 Sept. 1-2; #66 Dec. 2 Vol. 38-48: 1911: Mar. 9, Oct. 2 [20th anniversary] 1912: Mar. 19, Sept. 3 1913: Oct. 1 [Branner's installation as president] 1914: Jan. 23, Feb. 11, Feb. 16-17, Mar. 9, Oct. 6 1915: Sept. 1 1916: May 2 [D. S. Jordan retires]
  - LS death memorial: white satin with fringe, on metal rod. "In Memory of Leland", ARCH-AM-1995-30 (Box 1)
  - LSJU Fire Dept. Helmet, ca. 1969-1970, used in Encina Hall fire., ARCH-AM-1988-01 (Box 1)
  - Magnet: [class of ] 80 / Stanford Reunion Homecoming / October 19-22, 2000 [2 inch square], ARCH-AM-2007-004 (Box 1)
  - Mandolin and case. Case inscriptions (list of concerts) start in 1900 and end in 1902. Label inside mandolin: the New Washburn model 1897. Gourd-shaped body, mother of pearl inlay on neck. No strings; body badly cracked., ARCH-AM-2007-008 (Box 1)
  - Mandolin case, used by member of Mandolin club, ARCH-AM-2000-059 (Box 1)
  - Map, framed colored. Stanford Campus, by Della Taylor, 1938., ARCH-AM-2000-352 (Box 1)
  - Map, framed colored. Stanford University, by Ed Farmer, 1934., ARCH-AM-2000-353 (Box 1)
  - Map, Lands of Stanford, 1908, lithograph, Hermann Brothers., ARCH-AM-2000-354 (Box 1)
  - Marble from Art Museum; Plaster pieces showing original wall colors from Art Gallery; Wallpaper (fabric) from Art Gallery, ARCH-AM-2005-029 (Box 1)
  - Marble sculpture by William Couper of Jane L. Stanford's hands, ARCH-AM-2000-023 (Box 1)
  - Marble square with image of new wing of Iris B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts with "thank you January 24, 1999", ARCH-AM-2000-021 (Box 1)
  - Marshall ribbons from Commencement 2002 (2), ARCH-AM-2002-26 (Box 1)
  - master's hood, ARCH-AM-1982-10 (Box 1)
  - Masters hood, 1928, ARCH-AM-1982-11 (Box 1)
  - Masters hood, red inside, white border. 73x 47 cm., ARCH-AM-1984-43 (Box 1)
  - Match books, ARCH-AM-1984-52 (Box 1)
    1. 45th class reunion June 3, 1972. 1927-1972 2. 1869 East-West R.R.
  - Matchbook issued by Stanford Bank with slogan "Follow Stanford Sports" and image of Indian head headress on front and 1971 football schedule inside, ARCH-AM-2003-005 (Box 1)
  - Mayfield Curtain. 22 advertisements of local businesses painted in oils by Otto Schroeder. The article states it is 24x12, but it is apparently 8x18 feet., ARCH-AM-2006-009 (Box 1)
  - Medal awarded to H. T. Woodward, 1892, for 100 yard run, AAU, ARCH-AM-2000-056 (Box 1)
  - Medal awarded to LSJU by Ca. State Agric Society, 1904, for Jr. champion holstein bull. 1.75" diameter; silver metal, ARCH-AM-2000-025 (Box 1)
  - Medal awarded to LSJU by Ca. State Agric Society, 1911, for Grand champion holstein-fresian bull. 1.75" diameter; yellow metal, ARCH-AM-2000-026 (Box 1)
  - Medal in Blue Box. Box= 10x10x3cm. Medal= 7cm diam., re B O Railroad., ARCH-AM-2000-217 (Box 1)
  - Medal in box, 7 cm diam. Awarded to E.P. Cubberly, 1915, Butler Silver Medal., ARCH-AM-2000-243 (Box 1)
  - Medal in box. Medal 7cm diam. Awarded to E.P. Cubberly by Columbia Univ. N.Y.C. 1933., ARCH-AM-2000-242 (Box 1)
  - Medal in gray box. Medal 7.5cm diam. World's Columbian Exposition; given to John C. Branner., ARCH-AM-2000-253 (Box 1)
  - Medal in red box. 9x9x1 cm box, Louisiana Purchase Exhibition., ARCH-AM-2000-212 (Box 1)
  - Medal in red box. Box = 9x9x1cm, Universal Exposition, 1904 - St. Louis. Awarded to J.C. Branner., ARCH-AM-2000-213 (Box 1)
  - Medal in red box. Medal = 4cm, Panama Pacific International Expo. 1915. To Ellwood P. Cubberly. (Box 6x1 cm), ARCH-AM-2000-241 (Box 1)
  - Medal on ribbon Place Card of Leland Stanford, at 1889 Presidential Inagural (Harrison)., ARCH-AM-2000-206 (Box 1)
  - Medal on ribbon, 2.8cm diam. "Romma Commvnis Patris," in brown case 6x8x1 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-219 (Box 1)
  - Medal, 6x5cm. Profile of Napolean (?), ARCH-AM-2000-214 (Box 1)
  - Medal, J. H. Meyer, Le Exposition de Paris, 4.5 cm, ARCH-AM-1984-48 (Box 1)
  - Medal: 7.5cm. Daniel Webster in case., ARCH-AM-2000-205 (Box 1)
  - Medal: 7x4 cm. 11 September, SACRA Saecvlaria Celebrat, ARCH-AM-2000-204 (Box 1)
  - Medals awarded to Quate, ARCH-AM-2004-002 (Box 1)
    2004-002.1 IEEE Third Mellenium Medal, 2000 2004-002.2 IEEE Medal of Honor 1988 2004-002.3 National Medal of Science, 1992 2004-002.4 National Medal of Technology 2004-002.5 Aspen Highlands Silver Nastar
  - Medals received by Prof. S. P. Timoshenko, 1911-1962 (13 awards; 16 medals), ARCH-AM-1979-02 (Box 1)
    .1 Jourawski medal (1911) .2 Worcester Reed Warner medal (1935) (2 medals) .3 Benjamin Garver Lamme medal (1939) (2medals) .4 Louis Edward Levy medal (1944) .5 James Watt International medal (1947) (2 medals) .6 Trasenster medal (1948) .7 Elliott Cresson medal (1958) .8 James Alfred Ewing medal (1962) .9 R.F. - O. A.; .10 University of Zabreb (1969?) .11 Academie des Sciences (1966?) .12 National Academy of Scinces of the U.S. (1963) .13 Leonhardo Eulero Academia Scientiarum (1957)
  - Megaphone. 23x48 cm diam. Stanford Nebraska Rose Bowl, 1941. Red on top, white on bottom., ARCH-AM-2000-191 (Box 1)
  - Memorabilia - award and charm bracelet, ARCH-AM-1995-11 (Box 1)
    1. "Gold Spike" awarded to Fred Glover in honor of fundraising activities, 1974 2.Charm bracelet Fred made for his wife: boxing gloves, PBK pin, boxing medals
  - Memorabilia - dance card and box, ARCH-AM-1995-14 (Box 1)
    1. Dance card/program for junior prom 3/27/1903 in shape of plug ugly hat (3 dimensional) 2. box that holds photographs of Stanford, ca. 1903
  - Memorabilia - football, trophies, awards, and his hat, ARCH-AM-1994-04 (Box 1)
    1. Football signed by various S.U. coaches 2. 1938 trophy: "Area Contest - won by Fred Glover, 2/28/38" 3. 1953 loving cup, Stanford '33 - 20th reunion: Baldest 4. Award to Glover from Delta Tau Delta 5. 2 medals 6. Stanford Association Award, 1989 7. Centennial Award 1991 8. Fred's last hat
  - Memorabilia - tie and pennant, ARCH-AM-1993-03 (Box 1)
    1. Red tie with S. Indian painted on it 2. Red felt STANFORD pennant